# DELVIN MONGARE

7217 Jewel Ln N, Maple grove, MN 55311 <u>mongared0220@my.uwstout.edu</u> (612)-501-4445

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am an Applied Science graduate with four years of experience in supporting management in laboratory and field-based evaluation projects that include data processing, data entry and database maintenance, assisting in dissemination and utilization of evaluating information and other business and laboratory requirements.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Wisconsin-Stout – BS in Applied Science, Biotechnology, Biochemistry and Molecular Cell Biology. (2014-2019).

Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology – IT in Database Administration. (2012-2013).

#### **CORE STRENGTHS**

Desirable laboratory proficiency, strong communication skills both verbal and written (Ms. Office, presentations, patent lab book), excellent IT skills (ability to use established analytical packages and MySQL), broad and strong technical and scientific proficiency in Biological sciences, evidence of prior knowledge and ability to quickly establish knowledge of current status of research in specified fields, meticulous attention to detail and professionalism, strong desire to learn, collaborate and contribute, ability to prioritize projects and deliverables and meet deadlines in a timely manner, assist in ensuring compliance with policies per state regulation in administrative operations.

#### **RELEVANT SKILLS**

Quantitative and qualitative analysis, performing research under the instructions of a mentor/supervisor/ research associates, handle and analyze various samples from cell line development, cell culture development, purification and development, performing safety operations including training, basic hematology procedures, knowledge of chromatography, SDS-PAGE and electrophoresis, medical terminology proficiency.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

University of Wisconsin-Stout, Jarvis Hall Science Wing – Lab Technician (2015 - 2017 academic year) Cell Culture Company – Temp Research Assistant (2018 - 2019)
BrightStar Care, St Paul & Bloomington regions – Administrative Operations (2019 - 2020)
Olive Branch Estates – Part-time/ Full-time Nursing Assistant/supervisor (2016 - current)

### **AWARDS AND HONORS**

Chancellor's Award for Outstanding Academic achievement Award of Participation, 2016 academic year Stout Student Association Scholarships Undergrad International Tuition waivers (\$2500/semester since 2014) Sam E. Wood Scholarship and Stall Smith Intl student scholarship.

## References:

Kim Day, RN
Park Nicollet, St Louis Park- Nurse in Triage,
Professional Associate
952/239-8461
nurseday1@hotmail.com
Watertown, MN

Heidi Lohre, RN Olive Branch Estates Director of Nursing 952-448-4800 heidi@olivebranchestates.com 1850 Pioneer Trail, Chanhassen, MN

Jennifer Grant University of Wisconsin – Stout Instructor Phone number: 715/232-5025 grantje@uwstout.edu

Steve Madieka
Zandu Health Initiative owner
Instructor
952-479-0172
info@zanduhealthinitiative.org
10800 Lyndale Avenue South, Bloomington, MN

Courtney Meier
Direct Supervisor
BrightStar Care
952-300-3698
Courtney.meier@brightstarcare.com
8900 Penn Ave S, Bloomington, MN